Okay, this needs a explanation.
There's a food in America.
It's a vegetable
called "eggplant."
Eggplant.
-You have in China?
-Yeah, popular.
Oh.
Okay, Geshe Michael hate this
vegetable.
Okay?
Super-hate.
Okay? I really don't like
this vegetable.
Then I went to Paris, recently,
with my partner.
And, we ask our friend, Ben,
"What's a good restaurant?"
And he told us, "La Coupole."
La Coupole, right?
Seiji’s sister also sent me
to a good restaurant.
She lives in Paris.
So, my partner say,
"I...I'm order for you."
I said, "What am I having?"
They...they brought this thing.
I said, "What's that?"
"Au...Aubergine.
Aubergine.
Zi...This is aubergine."
I said, "This is not aubergine.
"This is eggplant!
"Don't give good name.
"Don't put different-looking...
Don't think I don't understand
eggplant."
Okay?
"Aubergine...this is
aubergine."
I don't want the "aubergine,"
okay?
Same...
crap,
different package.
Okay? Same crap, different package.
Okay? So, Xiaoping, give
Geshe Michael hundred dollar.
Okay, okay.